25th
3rd
Ganga barrage
Justice
later
Statute of limitations
means, a statute prescribing
a period of limitation.
This bill has been passed
in the Parliament.
This new law will be imposed
across India from 28th October.
Until now, this law was only applicable
to civil cases.
But now, according to this new law,
all criminal cases will also
come under the same jurisdiction.
All criminal cases,
15 years or older
that were cold cases
that is, which remained unsolved,
will now be closed forever.
Reports of violent protests
and arson against this new law,
have been reported from
various states in the country.
And one lady from Dehradun
has now become the face
of this pan-India agitation.
That's right. Sanjana Tiwari.
The mother, who has been
waiting for 15 years
to get justice for her daughter.
Exactly 3 days from now,
Aditi Tiwari's murder case
will be closed forever
and that will be the end of
a helpless mother's hope.
What do you think?
Will Aditi get justice?
(Aditi would have been
24 year old today)
An innocent eight-year-old girl
kidnapped from the Dussehra Fair.
The Police are investigating
the matter.
We have information that
the kidnapper has demanded a ransom.
According to sources,
the accused is a final
year student in a medical college
No, this is wrong.
It was a lady.
Aditi would have been
24 years old today.
It has been 15 years.
The Police haven't been able
to nab her murderer.
And now
after three days
the moment this law is passed
Aditi's case
will be closed.
But my fight won’t.
Until the government
revokes this law
I will go on an indefinite
hunger strike
in front of the police headquarters.
I won’t budge.
(Sanjana Tiwari’s indefinite hunger strike
against the Statue of Limitations)
Revoke the statute of limitations!
Fulfill our demands!
Balwant!
People have created a commotion
outside because of this law.
It's a circus out there!
It's just about wielding
some canes, Ma'am.
All of them will be back
in their senses.
Balwant Singh,
think beyond canes.
There's a difference between
the police and goons.
We've to behave appropriately
with the victim's family.
Where is the list
that the IG Sir asked for?
What are you gaping at me for?
Where are the files
of the 15-year old cases?
I've got record office
clerk on it.
(Records office)
Police Headquarters
There we go, Ma'am.
Sign here.
It's your mother.
Yes, Mother.
Listen. You left for work
without telling me.
I wanted to tell you something.
-Mr. Pant's son is coming to see you.
-Can we talk later, please?
-Just listen for a minute
He's a good man.  Settled abroad.
Mother
Look mother, I have no time
to waste on such petty topics.
Why are you losing your temper?
You've been waiting for 15 years.
He isn’t coming back!
And you're not
growing any younger.
It will be difficult to
get married in the older age.
Look msother, meeting and parting
isn't in our control.
What is to be, will be.
-Just hear me out
-Can I get back to work?
Is this a junk yard?
- New joining?
- Yes, Ma'am.
I've seen you somewhere.
Were you posted in Nainital?
Posting! Yeah, right.
He's being posted
with the protesters now-a-days
Inspector Yug Arya.
He's been all over the TV and newspapers.
He's a fake officer.
He can be charged with insubordination
and damaging police dignity.
What police dignity
is being damaged?
Is there any dignity left
to be damaged?
Whatever little that's left, will be finished
by old officers like you and the new law.
Fritter’s sauce from
Prakash’s famous shop.
You have them for free, don't you?
Have some shame!
wearing a sauce-stained
uniform in the office.
Thai massage! Not bad!
Seven star.
At Rs. 25,000 each,
3 for Rs.75,000.
-Shut up, you insolent chap
-Insolence is this Swiss made?
You're never on time.
What's the use?
Do one thing. Tell Ma'am
what's your salary.
Mr. Sub-inspector.
Tell her.
Rs. 24,718.
With your travel and daily allowance,
that comes to Rs.36,524.
Wow! You're walking around wearing
two years salary on your hand, Uncle!
-Uncle?
-Uncle.
Where's all this stuff
come from?
Did you pawn off your dignity
at Paltan bazaar?
Enough!
That's enough nonsense.
You need a degree to
talk nonsense.
M.A Psychology.
This is called criminal profiling, Ma'am.
You're calling me a criminal?
I'm not, brother. IPC Section 161 is.
Once you're charged with it,
you'll be locked up for a long time.
Don't cross your boundaries!
Yug Arya?
Have you noticed your own behaviour?
Despite being a police officer,
you sit with the protesters.
Get your pictures taken!
You've read the code of
conduct, haven't you?
You can be suspended in two minutes.
- Is this a joke?
- What else is it, Ma'am?
What is this?
I've seen this lady do the rounds
of the police station for 15 years.
She's been waiting for 15 years
for her daughter's murderer
to be caught and get justice. But no.
And now this law, after 3 days.
This is an official seal on the failure
of the police, Ma'am.
Now you tell me, Ma'am,
does police dignity
lie in protecting this law
or protesting against it?
Jai Hind!
Friendship, Service and Protection
Go, Save Your dignity
Ma'am, he
Yug Arya!
If you've such a big problem,
find another job. One with dignity.
In any case you aren't worthy
of being a police officer.
It wasn't a man. It was a lady.
C'mon boy. Run along now.
Uncle, chit!
(The one who took Aditi away
was a woman, not a man)
Hey, kid!
What are you doing here?
Where are your parents?
Get out of here!
Sorry.
-Are you alright, son?
-Yes.
Mr. Anthwal you are being
called for S.P. Sir’s meeting.
Project this.
Hello.
C'mon bro, give me something good.
We're in a bad shape.
Sir---
25th October. Between 7 pm and 8 pm.
Aditi Tiwari was kidnapped
from the Dussehra Fair.
On the same night
at 11 pm
the kidnapper messaged
from an unidentified number.
He demanded half a million in cash
and warned against informing the police.
But when Aditi didn't come home
even after the ransom was paid,
Mr. Hardev Tiwari filed a report
at the police station.
We took immediate action, Sir.
During the investigation, we got
a clue from the phone company.
The phone used to send the message
belongs to this boy, Sir.
Raghav Nautiyal.
He's a final year student
in Dehradun government medical college.
Sir, this boy has been absconding
for the past few days.
-Sir, I think
-You think?
You think?
It has been four days
and you are still thinking?
- Investigation is ongoing, Sir.
- Hey!
What do I do
with your investigation?
Should I shove it up my ass?
He's staring, a******---
He's done nothing for four days
and now he's staring back at me.
Investigation is ongoing
F******! You know everything.
His name, address and how he looks.
And stillyou guys can't nab
a 22-year-old pipsqueak!
On top of this, the media
is queuing up outside.
Do you know
Do you know whose daughter she is?
Hardev Tiwari. Poet king!
Last year, he won the highest
literary award in the country.
You know what that means?
The Chief Minister
has called me thrice.
My clothes are being ripped off
and you dumbfucks are
still jerking off.
Sir! Sir!
Sir,  Aditi Tiwari's
dead body has been found.
On the banks of River Ganga.
Move it!
Get there before the press!
Move your butts. Let's go!
Aditi!
Aditi! My child.
You were late!
You were too late!
He killed my Aditi.
Why?
Why couldn't you save her?
Why couldn't you nab
Raghav Nautiyal?
Why?
Calm down, Sanjana.
F***
Mills
(Aditi Tiwari kidnapping)
Ok, Sir
I'll take your leave.
The transfer
Today is my joining, Sir.
Should I leave then?
What a day you
chose for transfer.
What can I do Sir?
Sir, the toxicology report is clear.
There were vomit remnants in the mask
and polyester fibre
and alkylphenol ethoxylate
which is used in detergents
and pesticides.
Nothing else was found
in the nasal passage.
Even the lungs were clean.
So, it's clear that she did
not die of drowning.
She was asphyxiated.
Date and time of death?
The body was fully bloated,
so can't say anything concrete.
But according to our findings
I would lean on 28th of October.
Alright.
Nab Raghav Nautiyal, f******!
Sir, Raghav Nautiyal is not
the real perpetrator.
He is a clever medical student.
A state topper.
He's not foolish enough to send
the ransom message from his own phone.
If he didn’t send the message
Then why did he disappear?
How did your
state topper go missing?
Yes, Sir. His CDMA phone
is also switched off.
What else?
Because he knows someone is
framing him.
Raghav Nautiyal is the only son
of a wealthy man.
He had 1 million in his account
on the day of the kidnapping.
Why would he kidnap someone
for half a million?
There's some other game
being played here.
After the ransom message,
he withdrew half a million.
The exact amount that
the kidnapper demanded.
he called on this number.
For the first and last time.
And this is the number of
history sheeter Monty Tomar, a drug dealer.
He sells
hash, cannabis, heroin everything.
We should investigate this angle.
Shaurya Anthwal!
If you had paid any
attention at all to the case,
then you'd know that this is
no longer just a kidnapping case.
This is now a murder case,
you f*****!
Don't show me any angles.
I want the murderer. Nab him!
Get that?!
Stop your investigation,
Leave aside this angle crap.
Go with the team
and catch Nautiyal!
Get lost!
Shaurya!
Learn to work with
the team, Mr. Anthwal
Running around alone
won't get you anywhere.
You too stop Mr. Juyal
licking SP Bhatia’s ass
Dumm-kopf
"The one who took Aditi away
was a woman, not a man."
Slums
Monty Sir, he was looking for you.
I want dope.
Heroin.
Dope?
Dope costs money.
You have any?
Don't have money.
But I've customers.
I'll sell it ahead.
Such a great businessman?
With no money?
I don't buy that.
Guys, Frisk Mr. Riche Rich
Get back!
Take one step ahead
and I'll put a hole in you.
Get back!
Raghav Nautiyal called you
the day after Dussehra?
I don't know any Raghav Nautiyal!
You don't?
Was Nautiyal selling your dope
in medical college?
No!
Not Nautiyal, Sir.
His girlfriend.
It was her. She was
the one peddling drugs.
-Name?
-Don't know her name!
-You don't?
-No! I met Nautiyal only once, Sir.
He was the one who called me.
to settle his
girlfriend’s account
Where did he call you?
Where?
Tell Me!
In Panchachulli Textile mills.
25th
Hours
Aditi Tiwari
Autopsy Report.
Toxicology Report.
Alkylphenol Ethoxylates
Uses of Alkylphenol
Ethoxylates
Used as Detergent in textile mills.
3rd
Oh, These files?
These good for nothing windows!
Damn! Someone switch on
the generator! Mr. Rawat!
Mr. Rawat!
(Aditi Tiwari Kidnapping)
Inspector Yug Arya, come in. Over.
[rattled voice]
Mr. Rawat!
Inspector Yug Arya?
Yug!
Yug, can you hear me?
Where is the sound coming from?
Inspector Yug Arya.
Inspector Anthwal here. Over.
Inspector Yug, can you hear me?
How can the sound come from here?
Yug! Yug Arya.
Can you here me?
Respond, Inspector Yug Arya.
Yug Arya.
Can you here me?
Yug!
Inspector Yug Arya.
Inspector Anthwal here. Over.
Yug! Inspector Anthwal here.
Respond.
Hi, hello?
Inspector Yug Arya, I'm at
Panchachulli textile mills
The one you told me about.
In the dyeing shed,
near the bleaching tank
Raghav Nautiyal's dead body
has been found.
Nautiyal, from the Aditi Tiwari
kidnapping case.
Aditi Tiwari kidnapping case?
There's a syringe
stuck in his left arm.
But no other syringe marks
on his arms.
This means, Raghav
wasn't a drug addict.
So overdose is out of question.
It's clear that this is a murder
made to look like a suicide.
Raghav is a victim himself.
One thing is certain.
Raghav didn't kidnap Aditi.
It was someone else.
Which Which factory? Hello?
Are you high?
You were the one who
told me about this mill.
Which is in Ulaini.
Me?
When did I tell you?
I fail to understand you
I don't understand either.
Why did you forbid me
from coming to this mill?
What? I didn't
Mate! I didn't forbid anyone
Which branch are you from?
Which branch?
How do you know me?
Mr. Anthwal?
Hello!
Hello?
-Mr. Anthwal?
-Hey, hero!
Hello?
What world are you living in, bro?
This is not an iPhone.
It's a 15-year-old antique piece.
-It won't work.
- I've used it properly.
Transmission was on.
And now it is dead.
Hello, Mr. Anthwal?
You've lost your mind. Show me.
I just spoke
You're great, My Highness! Just great!
Where are your feet?
You had a conversation on a walkie
without batteries, your Highness!
Go home. Come back
when you're sober.
Nonsense
Wake up, Yug.
Wake up.
Inspector Yug Arya, I'm at
Panchachulli textile mills
The one you told me about.
In the dyeing shed,
near the bleaching tank
Raghav Nautiyal's dead body
has been found.
Nautiyal from the Aditi Tiwari
kidnapping case.
This is not an iphone.
It's a 15-year-old antique piece.
It won't work.
You had a conversation on a walkie
without batteries, your Highness!
In the dyeing shed,
near the bleaching tank
Raghav Nautiyal's dead body
has been found.
Alkylphenol Ethoxylate
Bleaching Tank 1
26th
69 hours